- question: "In the command line, how do you print working directory?"
  answer: "pwd"


- question: "In the command line, how do you see your computer's network name?"
  answer: "hostname"


- question: "In the command line, how do you make directory?"
  answer: "mkdir"


- question: "In the command line, how do you change directory?"
  answer: "cd"


- question: "In the command line, how do you list directory?"
  answer: "ls"


- question: "In the command line, how do you remove directory?"
  answer: "rmdir"


- question: "In the command line, how do you push directory?"
  answer: "pushd"

- question: "In the command line, how can you clear your stack?"
  answer: "irs -c"


- question: "In the command line, how do you pop directory?"
  answer: "popd"


- question: "In the command line, how do you copy a file or directory?"
  answer: "cp"


- question: "In the command line, how do you move a file or directory?"
  answer: "mv"


- question: "In the command line, how do you page through a file?"
  answer: "less"


- question: "In the command line, how do you print the whole file?"
  answer: "cat"


- question: "In the command line, how do you execute arguments?"
  answer: "xargs"


- question: "In the command line, how do you find files?"
  answer: "find"


- question: "In the command line, how do you find things inside files?"
  answer: "grep"


- question: "In the command line, how do you read a manual page?"
  answer: "man"


- question: "In the command line, how do you find which man page is appropritate?"
  answer: "apropos"


- question: "In the command line, how do you look at your environment?"
  answer: "env"


- question: "In the command line, how do you print some arguments?"
  answer: "echo"


- question: "In the command line, how do you export/set a new environment variable?"
  answer: "export"


- question: "In the command line, how do you exit the shell?"
  answer: "exit"


- question: "In the command line, how do you become super user root DANGER!"
  answer: "sudo"


